I was just so far from here. Focused on
my own way with never looking back to
this world and fear. There was nothing I
could do. There is nothing you said that
could make me realize I'm a lucky I was
just a bridge on the fire
begging for help begging for just my try
to be some
try
Yeah. Heat.
to go.
Can't see through the time.
>> Hey, Scoo. Want to eat behind the barn
again today? I broke open my piggy bank
to buy celery sticks and peanut butter
so we can make ants on a log. Damn, that
[__] sounds legit, [__]
>> Ants on a log? That's loser baby stuff.
Hey, sweetie Bell. You're not a baby,
are you?
>> No, she's just a smelly queer. She wants
to go eat sticks behind the barn with
her girlfriend because she's a queer.
Hey, Diamond Tiara, did you hear that
[__] I called Sweetie Bell a weird gay
kid.
>> Did you hear what I said, [__] I said,
"Wasn't that funny?"
>> I am not a queer.
>> I'm just saying what we're all thinking,
you little gay freaks.
>> Hey, lay off her. Sweetie Belle can
choose to eat with any pony she wants.
>> You don't Can you shut up, [__] You're
drinking Shasta Cola. Like, omg [__]
you can't even afford Coca-Cola. Like,
omg, [__] you can't even afford
Coca-Cola. It's probably because your
parents left you with your two
homosexual aunts so they could go have
butt sex in the Amazon rainforest.
>> Actually, Scoo, I think I want to go
make the ants on a log by myself.
Wo! Pizza Lunchables. That's the good
[__] Hell yeah. It's got those little
pepperonis and everything. It even comes
with a cookie for dessert. You know,
Apple Bloom. I think I might know a
super turbo totally heterosexual idiot
who could use a build your own
Lunchables pepperoni pizza right about
now.
Skittle Apple Bloom. Check it. Sweets.
Apple Bloom brought the goods.
Lunchables pizza party. One rule. No
jerks allowed. Are you girls, but do you
really want to be seen eating with me?
Our classmates might tease you for
catching a case of the gay or something.
That's not how it works. You'd have to
actually be gay for that. Wait, you're
not, are you?
I'm going to go take a fat dump. Don't
touch my Lunchables. I might be for
real. I didn't think I was, but I just
feel I feel different while I'm around
you. It's not like friendship I have
with Apple Bloom. And I know it's weird.
And I know every pony is probably going
to think I'm disgusting.
Wo wo chill. You're not disgusting. I
mean, yeah, it's a little gay, but
ponies assume I'm also gay for some
reason because I spent 2 years of my
life collecting Rainbow Dash hairs to
make this costume. What we do isn't gay.
It's like a hobby. It doesn't make me
gay because I want Rainbow Dash to hold
me down and [__] in my mouth. Me wanting
to be in a sexual relationship with
Rainbow Dash and get married to her. Is
it gay? God, I want to have kids with
Rainbow Dash someday. I think our first
child will be named ass blaster
Thunderbolt. That would be cool as [__]
You mean you're not mad? Sweetie Bell,
if I got mad every time some pony wanted
to go on a date with me, I'd be furious
every hour of every day. Thank you,
Scoo. You're a good friend.
Next time some pony gives you crap about
being a super turbo homosexual idiot,
just remember they don't get invited to
the ants on a log party. More like logs
of [__] Am I right, girls?
Coco, put that back. You know we don't
have the money for Kelloggs. Let's make
this quick. I got to get home and empty
my ass of [__]
>> Siri's finally using the sweet ropes I
recommended as replacement for
cigarettes. I'm glad to know she's
finally changing for the better.
>> No one will ever know these are going up
my ass instead of in my mouth.
What is this?
>> Horse toilet paper for your butt.
You bought two ply toilet paper. Did I
not just get through explaining how
broke a [__] we are?
>> If I'm going to be the one wiping your
crusty bum, then I think I should at
least get some say in the sorts of
toilet paper we buy. It always tears and
I get poo poo on my hooves since you
only buy the cheap brands.
>> Only because you scrunch when you should
be folding. You smoothrained homunculus.
>> I don't get it. If you don't like me,
then why do you even keep me around?
You're white and I'm a French woman.
That's really good for PR.
Moshi Moshi S e Deu. The change Ling
Kingdom. Oh, sorry. Yes, we deliver. Do
you even have mailboxes? I'll get on it
right away.
>> Who is that?
>> Just a roach with fashion delusions.
Once a dress delivered, probably to wear
over her gross exoskeleton. Well, are we
going to do it?
>> Delivered to the changeling kingdom. Are
you mad? That place is right next to the
Waffle House. She is lucky I didn't
report her to pest control.
>> Hey, here's an idea. Why don't we just
go ask Princess Cadence and Shining
Armor to send a couple of royal guards
so we can deliver it to the ghetto?
So, how did you enjoy your Uber ride
with Rarity's Royal Ride Share?
>> Fine.
>> No need to thank me, darling. Your
gratitude is adorable, but ultimately
irrelevant and wasting precious time I
could be using to make more Uber money.
But I do thank you, Koko, for not being
black. Now, before anyone gets offended,
remember that I am a white woman, so I
am not racist. I haven't said a single
slur. I have never ever called anyone
the n-word today. Now, Coco, sweetie, if
you would be so kind, please go ahead
and rate this ride five stars because I
am a white woman.
Turn the phone towards me while you do
it.
>> We're not going to tip.
>> That's fine, Sor. You already uplifted
my spirits today with that amusingly
hideous fake French accent.
>> This is my real accent.
>> Oh, I am so sorry, but not for what I
said. I'm sorry for you having to live
sounding like that in my 2024 Nissan
Versa.
>> Welcome to my throne room, peasants. You
can bask in my glory.
>> Shining armor. Since when were you the
princess of the Crystal Empire?
>> Have I not always been the royal beacon
of grace and governance? I thought
Cadence was the princess.
>> Me a princess? That's silly. I've always
been her loyal and chiseled protector. I
brought you your chai latte, your
highness. Is it to your liking, [__]
>> Is this even decaf? I said I wanted
decaf.
>> Everyone who drinks coffee knows decaf
is basically flavored water and in fact
actually decreases from the coffee
enjoying experience. I am not doing
that. I don't care if you're an olicorn
princess shining armor because to me,
you're still my loser brother whose only
accomplishment in life was being born
with a sharp jawline. You're just a
>> just a what?
>> Just a pretty pretty princess.
Get me on that membership plan. I'm
tired of losing. I want to get jacked.
It is done.
Knowledge is power, but power is also
power.
Shining armor, seductive, mind- tickling
voice won't work on me anymore. Not now
that I've obtained the greatest strength
of all, self-positivity,
and the ability to crush watermelons
between my thighs.
Sister, you're back just in time for
rehabilitation.
Come, gaze into my eyes and let us talk.
Huh, that's curious.
Your powers of seduction meant something
once you tempt a switch. when I was weak
before I achieved the ultimate human
form.
I'm here to fix reality where I'm the
only one that matters and you're just
the dorky hetero.
>> Wait, Twilight, we still need their
help.
>> A customer from the Changling Kingdom
wants this delivered today. They already
paid full price.
>> You interrupted my magical fists for a
delivery mission, little ponies. Do I
have to punch you, too? Twilight, you
may change us back. We won't fight you,
but only on one condition.
>> Say it quick. My biceps need to punch
something.
>> If we're going to the Changeling
Kingdom, then I want to take this
opportunity to bring an end to our
eternal enemy once and for all.
>> Look guys, a mime.
>> She came to us crying and begging for a
job. So, we hired her as the Crystal
Empire's own personal court mime. Hey
Trixie, we're heading out to assassinate
the neighboring monarch. Do you want to
come?
Oh, come on. It might be fun.
We'll pay you.
This is it. The majestic capital of the
insect underclass. You know you've
entered changeling territory when
streets are named after prominent
changeling figures. Stay close. You
don't want to be caught alone around
these changelings. You know the urban
ones.
>> Urban ones.
>> Don't give me that look, Koko. I'm not
racist. I respect changelings. I even
babysat one once. I just think it's of
the utmost importance that we're
cautious of our surroundings. Watch out.
He's aggressive.
Look, you never know who's who in this
hood. Changelings grew up on deception.
>> That's a pretty racist thing to say.
Changelings are creatures just like us
with their own culture.
>> My last birthday party was at a waffle
house. Look, there's the queen of the
changelings house. I suspect that
because it's the only one not broken
into.
>> Changeling drone number 13,420.
Why the frack haven't you finished your
godamn KFC famous bowl from the $5 value
menu yet?
>> Mom, why don't I look like any of my
brothers and sisters? I already ate the
chicken nuggets. All that's left is the
mashed potatoes. It's too spicy.
>> Spicy potatoes.
>> They use a lot of black pepper. Mom, is
it weird that I crave mayonnaise like
all the time?
>> [__] I was afraid of this, but suddenly
it all makes sense. your odd fascination
with true crime podcasts and listening
to perfect by Ed Sheeran. Changeling
drone 13,420.
I don't mean to scare you, but I think
you inherited a dangerously large amount
of white pony jeans.
>> Golly G willilickers. I can't be white.
I listen to the Jonas Brothers all the
time. Fall decor and ice coffee. [__] I
think I'm white as [__] Oh my god.
>> You are not one of us and you will never
be one of us. I will keep you around for
EBT card benefits, but other than that,
you are never to leave this shitty ass
apartment unless a driveby happens. Then
I guess you can come with us to the
neighborhood weather shelter for safety.
>> Child protective services are here. Take
your brothers and sisters and hide them
in the attic before they find out I'm
building another army of child soldiers.
>> No one is answering.
>> Typical of a changeling, violence is all
they know.
Damn [__] you live like this.
>> Break as many windows you want, [__]
I'm still not paying taxes.
>> You think that'll work on me?
>> Hooray. It worked.
>> Mission accomplished. Let's go home.
Miss Siri, that was our client.
>> Well, we're already committed to this.
Siri Paula May always gets the job done.
Fetch the ribbons, my [__]
>> [__] it's a drive by.
>> I like Siri. I was the one drinking your
oat milk.
>> I lie too. I actually like your bull
cut.
Hey, Scoots. Do you want to go to CeCe's
Pizza? Like as our first date? I am this
close to kicking your day, weird little
ass. Also, we just ate a pizza
Lunchable. Why do you want more pizza?
Oh my god, if you two aren't the most
adorable, emotionally confused queers I
have ever seen in my life.
>> Flawless Sparkle Moon, the mirror pony
>> in the flesh. Flawless Sparkle Moon, age
27, technically still enrolled here as a
Philly. May I chaperone your little
pizza date? You two are just too
precious for me to let wander
unsupervised. Think of me as your
whimsical adult oversight with no social
boundary skills. You're having a hard
time making friends here because you're
old.
>> Me being older than most of these kids'
mothers doesn't automatically mean I'm
old, you shitty little brat. We're all
still learning to drink a glass of water
with two hooves. We're on the same team.
>> A rainbow dash hair. Give it to me.
>> Only if you promise to tell everyone in
school you're my friend.
>> A rare purple hair, the kind located
nearest to Rainbow Dash's ass crack. And
you expect me to believe its
authenticity just by your word?
It's real. Okay, Flawless. From this day
onward, you are the honorary fourth
member of the Rainbow Dash fan club.
Like every pony, the gay little Philly
needs old lady babysitter to go buy
Cece's pizza. I knew you were a baby
sweetie Bell. Like, oh my god, someone
needs to put you in a freaking diaper
and then change it when you [__] out
your [__] This is why my hair is
braided like a cool Jedi Knight while
your hair curls like some gay guy's
butthole after it was used six or seven
times by another gay guy. And you wonder
why you will never be cool. Now, if you
stupid [__] ass babies will excuse my
sexy ass, I'm going to hit the red light
district and suck a shitload of balls
for a shitload of money because these
millennial hipster glasses don't pay for
themselves. And I'm also going to buy a
Nintendo Switch, too, and a couple
games, which you also can't afford
because you're just a couple of broke
boys. Maybe I'll hit Starbucks on the
way to after I'm done hitting the
streets, if you know what I mean.
>> Hey, kid. I can feel the magic stirring
within you. You're not just going to
stand there and let them talk about your
repressed little cinnamon bun like that.
Just imagine something terrible
happening to her and your abilities will
do the rest.
>> I want her to poop and I want her to
poop now.
>> Oh my god, there's poop coming out my
ass. What the hell? It just won't stop.
God, someone like help. Oh my god, this
hurts. Can someone just put tape over my
[__] or something? It won't stop.
>> I'm not done with you yet. I'm going to
make an example out of you so everyone
can see what happens when you pick on a
member of the Rainbow Dash fan club.
>> You've made your point, Sketaloo. Be the
bigger pony and put a stop to this. Now,
>> she's been bullying us all year, Miss
Julie. And you did nothing. Don't
pretend like you care.
>> Children, look away. I don't want you to
experience what is about to happen.
Go invisible. Scootaloo blast.
>> Oh [__] Scootaloo shot a magic blast
and it really is invisible. But how do
we know where the blast is going? Oh
wait, Silver Spoon is dead.
Please.
>> What do you mean you're leaving the
Rainbow Dash fan club? We're supposed to
be a team. I'm sorry, Scoo, but I don't
think my family will let me play with
you anymore if you're going to make
ponies [__] You [__] This is the
ultimate betrayal to our Lord and
Savior, Rainbow Dash. Now I am going to
have to shoot you. Go scoot blast.
Oh my god, Diamond Tiara is going to
throw herself off the Ponyville
Schoolhouse.
>> Do a flip.
>> Don't do it, Diamond Tiara. You're only
4 and a half years old. You still have
your whole life ahead of you.
>> Are you serial right now? You actually
just tried to pelt me with giant ass
boulders a moment ago. Like right after
killing my gal pal, Silver Spoon. I
don't want to hear a thing you have to
say, and I don't trust you not to kill
me regardless. So, no. That [__] had it
coming and you know it. Flawless. Can't
you go up there and grab her?
>> No can do. I'm on a list.
Do you know why I bullied you guys? It's
because I was projecting my own
insecurities onto you because I'm also
gay and that makes me hate myself like a
lot because I lie and tell people that
Kiana Reeves is my celebrity crush when
it's actually Alice from Twilight. I
don't know that actress's name. I just
know her as Alice.
Actually, I take that back. Jasper from
Twilight is pretty hot. Okay, maybe I'm
not gay.
>> Oh, snap. I didn't realize someone else
was going to jump today. This is so
embarrassing. You can carry on. I'll uh
I'll just go after you.
>> You were planning to end it all today,
too. But you don't look very gay.
>> No, I'm just black. Also, my mom sucks.
>> Dang, my mom sucks, too. Mostly just
balls, though, because she's a huge
[__] Also, she hits me.
>> It really is a small world.
>> Why are you throwing yourself off a
building just because you're black? I
mean, it's not like that's something you
have control over. Being born inferior
is natural sometimes. Why are you
throwing yourself off a building cuz
you're gay when over 95% of Ponyville is
also gay? It doesn't make any sense. It
would make sense if you were black.
>> I guess you're right. I mean, it could
be worse. Like, I could be a burn
victim.
>> Some of us take offense to that. No, you
don't. Okay.
>> Hey, I'll tell you what. We're gathering
quite the crowd here, so I won't jump if
you won't.
>> Okay. I guess I still didn't see the
sequel to Megan Megan 2.0 yet, but I
hear it sucks since they turned it into
an action movie, so I don't know. I
guess I won't jump. Unless that movie is
bad, then I might jump later. We'll see
how it goes.
You walk ahead of me. I don't trust
black ponies not to steal my money since
Nightmare Moon is black and she stole
daylight from the world one time and her
white sister had to beat her up.
Flawless. I just want to thank you for
talking me down. Even though you're old,
you're you're pretty cool. So, you can
have this shirt my mom found at Goodwill
but can't wear because her balloon tits
are just massive.
>> All right.
All right. All right.
>> I can't believe you even thought about
it.
>> I thought it would give everybody
something fun to talk about for once. I
mean, it would have made for the perfect
headline, don't you think? Local rich
girl too beautiful for this world. I bet
I would be trending for at least a
weekend.
>> But Diamond,
>> what? You think anyone would actually
miss me? I bet you and your little gang
would make a party out of it or some
[__]
>> That isn't true.
>> Oh my god. Here we go. Cue the
sentimental farm girl speech.
>> Let me cook. The chef is in the kitchen.
You think you're being tragic, but
you're just being mean. When you die,
yeah, sure it's over for you. But what
about the rest of us? We'd have to live
with it. We'd have to carry all of that
hurt, wondering if we could have stopped
you. That's the cruel part that I bet
you weren't thinking about when you were
up there.
>> Wow. I haven't really thought about it
like that.
>> You're making me feelings.
Gross. I hate it.
>> Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh. Is this totally
happening right now? What's happening?
>> Shush. I'm trying to listen.
>> What you got there, Cadence? Yeah, we
wanted to give the other Cadence and
Shining Armor a gift. Do you think
they'll like it?
>> That would be pony trafficking. So, no.
I'm going to have to release her back to
the custody of the Changeling Kingdom
after I return you both to normal.
>> So, if we go through with this, I won't
be a princess anymore.
>> Shiny, what did I tell you? It doesn't
matter what we are. I'll love you all
the same. You'll always be my princess.
>> Yes, I know.
shining armor.
>> Actually, I think I much prefer what I
am now.
>> Shining armor, listen to me. This isn't
you. Let me change you back to who
you're meant to be. Why would I ever go
back to being some dorky stallion prince
when I can be a white woman
is not about you. It's about you. She's
trying your name and she looks exactly
the same.
>> You showed me all I needed to see. Even
if my brother's mind is asleep, his
heart's still alive and well.
>> Now it's time for him to wake up.
Huh? Twilight, I feel kind of funny. Did
something happen?
>> Creep. How dare you gallop into my mind
without permission?
>> This isn't your mind escape. It belongs
to my brother, the real shiny armor.
>> Okay, hold on. I'm confused.
>> Okay, so we kind of need to destroy this
female version of you or you might not
be able to wake up again.
>> If this is my mind, then technically I
should be able to manifest anything I
want here.
>> Yeah, I guess so. Theoretically,
suck [__] Who wants to drink beer
and get their balls sucked?
>> Bro, why did you manifest my hot
teacher? Princess Celestia's sinister
half, also known as Daybreaker. Also
known as Gaybreaker because she's feared
in the gay community because she's known
for being so hot she can turn gay
stallions like straight [__]
>> Why do you know this?
>> Sexual boundaries are a myth. Go
fireball.
We ended up here
to see what we've lost. Stop when you
see a bit better.
>> Twilight, I know you want your brother
back,
>> but I I don't want to lose him.
>> You're not going to lose each other
because whenever Shining Armor and
Cadence are together, you will be, too.
Am I going to remember any of this when
I change back? Probably not.
>> Now announcing a new Ocoin chosen by the
divine wisdom of the sun.
>> Oh my god, it's happening. Celestia saw
me dive into my brother's collapsing
psyche to save him from the clutches of
evil. Citizens of Equestria, today is a
momentous day as we welcome a new
oleicorn among us. Princess Coco Palm O.
>> Okay, now this is some [__] A yo,
Princess, what did she do?
>> She showed incredible spirit today
helping her boss deliver a dress.
>> What's she even the princess of? Being
soft-spoken and crying in public.
>> She is the princess of creating a
healthy work environment. It is a very
nuanced domain.
>> But Suri hates her.
>> Well, now that I know that, maybe I
wouldn't have made her an olicorn.
>> Can I be an icorn? I saved my brother's
life.
>> And Koko bought Sori a coffee once.
Isn't friendship wonderful?
>> I feel like you're dodging my question.
>> Oh, and shining armor. I do so love a
stallion who has appreciation for the
divine. If you ever wish to explore such
subjects further, I might just be able
to let Daybreaker out to play. Give me a
call sometime, Captain.
>> Oh my god, I've been bugnapped.
>> Chrysalis, me and Shining Armor talked
some things over KFC, and we think it's
time for a fresh start.
>> You guys are finally going to have sex
with me?
>> No, as friends. You guys are finally
going to have sex with me as friends.
>> Chrysalis, there's more to life than
sexual intercourse.
>> Prove it then by having sex with me.
>> How would that prove anything?
>> It wouldn't. I just want sex.
>> That's gross.
>> No, you are. Luring me into your
heterosexual traps like this, then
recoiling in shame when I offer myself
to your husband.
>> Because he's a married stallion. We have
a connection built on years of trust and
love. What do you have? Well, I mean, we
did have sex once or twice.
>> You brainwashed him.
>> He didn't say no.
>> Because you brainwashed him.
>> Can I say something?
>> Stay out of this.
>> Shiny, be honest. Who do you like more?
>> Listen, [__] I am a monogous husband.
I like vanilla milkshakes and vibing out
to perfect by Ed Sheeran. I do not want
to be the vanilla in your ice cream
sandwich.
>> Oh, he's shy. That's adorable.
>> Shiny. No ponies pressuring you to make
a choice.
>> Don't call me shiny. Only Cadence and my
mommy can call me that.
>> But you did say you wanted to start
fresh, right?
>> Very well, Queen Chrysalis. Princess
Cadence, you win. Though it is not
something I personally desire, if this
will be what it takes to prove
friendship and symbolically unify two of
Equestria's most powerful kingdoms, then
I will be the one to die on this hill,
unwilling as it may be, because I love
my country and its ponies. Tonight I
stand between two powerful forces that
ought to be united for diplomacy. No.
For all of Equestria, I will have lots
of heterosexual sex with not one, but
two of Equestria's ruling monarchs after
we get back from Red Lobster in hopes
that together we can build better and
forge a most beautiful future for those
who come after. Though it is not
something I want, only I'm strong enough
to make such a sacrifice.
Diplomacy achieved.
>> Treaty approved.
>> The centuries of war between the Crystal
Empire and Changeling Kingdom has come
to an end.
Now there is only friendship land.
you in the yellow light saying that boy
you
said it was a coincidence but you can't
explain that I'm not going to
I should smile
I knew I always would I want to meet you
slow down I want to meet you soon I want
to meet you I can't speak
or dare across
I want to meet you at a slow dance. I
want to meet you at a soul. I want to
meet you, but I can't speak
or dead across the room. But I am trying
stuck beneath the spinning
familiar.
Struck by your impression like all of
those next to you. I will try to stand
and make it down the hall but in the
sound.
I'm barely here at all. I want to meet
you slow down. I want to meet you right
soon. I want to meet you but I can't
speak
or dare across the room. I want to meet
you at a slow dance. I want to meet you.
I want to meet you, but I can't speak
or dead across the room. But I am
trying.
>> So, what was it like being Princess
Shiny? I mean, you had wings and your
hair was all swishy.
>> Honestly, I don't even remember half of
it.
>> You were kind of scary. I'm glad you're
back to normal, though. Not that
Princess Shiny wasn't fabulous. I mean,
she had great style, but I like you
better when you're you. You're cool and
strong and brave, and you don't have to
try and brainwash ponies to get them to
like you.
>> Actually, um I never told anyone this,
but I always wanted a big brother,
someone who'd look out for me. Not
because I'm weak or helpless. I can sew
a 100 dresses in three days if I have
to.
If you ever need any help with royal
duties, I'm your guy. Big brother mode
activated.
>> Oh wow,
you're going to make me cry in public.
And this ice pop is already making my
muzzle sticky. But I don't care because
now I have a big brother and not even
Suri can say that. Well, unless you also
adopt her, too, which actually don't do
that. She'll make you carry her purse.
My first official night as an honorary
member of the Rainbow Dash fan club. The
girls will never know what hit them when
I pop in with this limited time
exclusive Fantastic 4 pizza from Little
Caesars.
>> Oh my god, it really is an action movie.
What were they thinking? I really wish I
didn't come here. I hope they don't
cancel the Megan series altogether.
She's too good of a character to just
throw away, but I have no faith in
Blumhouse.
>> Are we really going to let some pony
like Flawless Sparkle Moon in the
Rainbow Dash fan club? Of course not.
She's way too weird. I mean, come on,
sweetie. She talks to herself in the
mirror at school. What 27year-old does
that? It would make us look like total
jokes. The only reason we're pretending
she's in the club is cause when she's
around it makes bullies back off. That's
it.
Hey, Flawless. What are you doing out
here? Aren't you heading inside?
>> It seems I'm not welcome here on the
account that they think I'm a huge butt
head.
>> Okay, see you around.
>> Yeah, see you in class tomorrow. I guess
it's fine. I'm fine. I'm the
one-of-a-kind pony for Mirror World.
I've lived through mirror implosions. I
can handle being rejected by Phillies.
Flawless. Have you been crying? No. Your
mascara is running.
What the hell happened to you?
>> I was trying to start an anti-Stallion
protest. Stallions threw produce at me.
I'm not mad, just mildly disappointed.
Do you girls ever just want to fall
asleep in a garbage bin and let the
trash accept you?
>> Hey, is that the brand new limited
edition hot and ready Fantastic 4 pizza
from Little Caesars for just $7.99?
>> Yeah, I got it for four. Never mind. For
us, it is split into four, like the name
for sections for four little ponies.
>> I'm like the thing, right? Physically
scarred but with a heart of gold. No,
you're the Human Torch because I set you
on fire that one time. Flawless is the
thing because we don't even know what
the hell she is. And I'm Mr. Fantastic
because I'm really smart.
>> No, I am because I'm the man in this
relationship. You're Sue Storm because
you're the weak female.
>> Hey, I guess this pizza is like us after
all.
>> I just said that, dumbass. Are you
stupid?
>> For a mime, you're doing a whole lot of
talking.
>> For a [__] with a mouth, you're doing a
whole lot of not gagging on my balls.
And so Flawless Sparkle Moon sat down on
the grass between them and ate her
pizza. Her mascara was ruined, but she
didn't care because even if a treehouse
full of kids didn't want her, she was
surrounded by a family that did. So,
what was your favorite part of the
episode?
>> The scene where the baby tried to off
herself.
>> Bro, shut up. I was addressing the
viewer.
>> How was I supposed to know? There's more
than one pony in this room, [__]
>> Why would I be asking you? So, what was
your favorite part of the episode?
>> I already asked that.
>> They didn't have the time to answer
before you turned into a catty [__]
So, what was your favorite part of the
episode?
>> This episode was brought to you by
Little Caesars.
>> Can we say that
>> if this episode was sponsored by Little
Caesars, then why was every pony eating
KFC?
>> Shining Armor, can you please shut up
and let me talk?
Hurry up.
>> I forgot what I was going to say. Hurry.
Say something funny.
>> Knock knock.
>> Who's there?
>> I forgot the rest.
>> That's understandable. Statistically
speaking, humor effectiveness is
determined by a combination of timing
and delivery style. I'd say my comedic
versatility score is at least 27% higher
than yours due to our vastly different
life experiences.